

IVAN FLORES HURTADO

Product Management

CONTACT

iafhurtado@gmail.com

(174) 239 70774

github.com/iafhurtado

🏠 Hamburg, Germany

CERTIFICATES

META - FRONTEND DEVELOPER PROFESSIONAL

2023

Coursera

Complete React Developer in 2023

Udemy

EDUCATION

KÜHNE LOGISTICS UNIVERSITY

2016

Master of Science in Global Logistics Hamburg, Germany

ABOUT

Experienced leader with a knack for building products that customers love to use. My strength is recognizing valid and actionable feedback from plain noise and crafting a plan to reach our goals. The key is to bring all stakeholders together and efficiently move an idea from discovery to post-launch support.

CORE QUALIFICATIONS

Fire Starter
Strategic Thinking
Aligning Stakeholders
Team Leadership
Roadmapping & Execution
UX Design & Research

Setting Product Vision/Strategy Agile Facilitator Cross-Functional Expertise Entrepreneurial Mindset Third-Party Integrations DevOps (CI-CD)

EXPERIENCE

PRODUCT LEADERSHIP & DESIGN

Selbständig - Freelancer | Sep 2020 - Present

- · Work with the executive suite to hone the vision, strategy and roadmap of the product
- Think through Jobs-To-Be-Done and how to bring practical solutions to market
- Draft user-interaction diagram and front-end interfaces (Figma)
- Provide a sense of direction by posing the right questions and having the tough conversations
- Gather feedback from users to improve on the next iteration
- Documentation and recording of most important information for the community

PRODUCT TEAM LEAD

FujiDAO Labs OÜ | Feb 2022 - Nov 2022

- Advocate as the voice-of-the-customer inside the development team
- Facilitating agile practices such as Brainstorming and Retrospective sessions
- Holding weekly feedback calls with stakeholders to solicit insights from front-lines
- Orchestrating work among different teams (Web vs iOS vs Android vs Agent)
- Executing the product strategy and holding everyone accountable



CONTACT

iafhurtado@gmail.com

(174) 239 70774

github.com/iafhurtado

Hamburg, Germany

EDUCATION (CONT.)

UNIVERSITY OF ARIZONA

2010-2012

Bachelor of Science in Operations Management Tucson, Arizona

PIMA COMMUNITY COLLEGE

2008-2010

Business Administration Major

Tucson, Arizona

UDEMY CERTIFICATES

The complete Javascript Course

Jonas Schmedtmann

Learn Python Programming Masterclass

Tim Buchalka

EXPERIENCE

PRODUCT MANAGER

Kühne + Nagel | Mar 2019 - Dec 2020

- Align stakeholders around a common roadmap (Customers, Dev Teams, Operations and Sales)
- Ensure continuous deployment across all Spring microservices
- Engineer requirements from customer feedback
- Brainstorm and mock-up interfaces to give designers and engineers as product perspective
- Evangelized Agile development and staying nimble inside the Dev team

PRODUCT OWNER

ShareHouse GmbH & Co. KG | May 2018 - Mar 2019

- Startup's first full-time employee
- Coordinated with an agency house to make sure product requirements were aligned
- Groom the backlog and estimate effort for tasks and user stories
- Helped interview new colleagues to grow the team up to 18 teammates
- Tested new releases for quality assurance and frictionless deployment

CO-FOUNDER & CEO

Clinch Logistics GmbH | Apr 2017 - Feb 2019

- Secured seed funding to build our MVP from Angel Investors in Hamburg
- · Hired core team of engineers
- Build in public at the Digital Hub Logistics in the Hafencity and participated in an accelerator from NUMA in Mexico City
- Conducted business development calls with early customers
- Gathered feedback from early users and integrated back into our backlog